let quizz = [
    {
    question: "Which word does NOT belong with the others ?",
    option: [
        "inch ",
        "ounch ",
        " yard",
        " centi meter",
    ],
    answer: 2,
},
{
    question: "Cup is to coffee as bowl is to ?",
    option: [
        "dish ",
        "soup ",
        " spoon",
        " food",
    ],
    answer: 2,
},
{
    question: "SLAPSTICK : LAUGHTER",
    option: [
        "genre : mystery ",
        " satire : anger ",
        " horror : fear",
        "mimicry : tears",
    ],
    answer: 3,
},
{
    question: "What day does Uma do her task?",
    option: [
        "Monday ",
        "Wednesday",
        "Thursday ",
        "Saturday ",
    ],
    answer: 3,
},
{
    question: "Which city got the most rain?",
    option: [
        "Last Sand ",
        "1Mile City",
        "New Town",
        "Olliopolis ",
    ],
    answer: 1,
},
{
    question: "SCD, TEF, UGH, ____, WKL",
    option: [
        "CMN ",
        " UJI",
        "VIJ ",
        "IJT ",
    ],
    answer: 3,
},
{
    question: "CMM, EOO, GQQ, _____, KUU",
    option: [
        "GRR ",
        "GSS",
        "ITT ",
        "IIS ",
    ],
    answer: 4,
},
{
    question: " 53, 53, 40, 40, 27, 27, ... What number should come next?",
    option: [
        " 12",
        " 14",
        "27 ",
        " 53",
    ],
    answer: 2,
},
{
    question: "28 25 5 21 18 5 14",
    option: [
        "11 5 ",
        "10 7 ",
        "11 8 ",
        "10 5 ",
    ],
    answer: 1,
},
{
    question: "3 5 35 10 12 35 17",
    option: [
        "22 35",
        "35 19 ",
        "19 35",
        "19 24 ",
    ],
    answer: 3,
},
{
    question: "Look at this series: F2, __, D8, C16, B32, ... What number should fill the blank?",
    option: [
        "A16 ",
        "G4 ",
        "E4 ",
        "E3 ",
    ],
    answer: 3,
},
{
    question: "Look at this series: VI, 10, V, 11, __, 12, III, ... What number should fill the blank?",
    option: [
        "II ",
        "IV",
        "IX ",
        "14 ",
    ],
    answer: 2,
},
{
    question: "Which word does NOT belong with the others?",
    option: [
        "bud ",
        "rose ",
        " tulip",
        " daisy",
    ],
    answer: 1
},
{
    question: "SPY : CLANDESTINE",
    option: [
        "accountant : meticulous",
        "furrier : rambunctious",
        "shepherd : garrulous ",
        "lawyer : ironic",
    ],
    answer: 1
}

]